A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation, 14
  - PLANS 1707-1748, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 21)
    Plans 1749-1753 are not contained in the archival collection.
  - PLANS 1754-1812, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 11, Folder 29)
  - PLANS 1813-1849, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 22)
  - PLANS 1850F-1874, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 11, Folder 32)
  - PLANS 1875-1898, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 12, Folder 41)
  - PLANS 1899-1934, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 23)
  - PLANS 1935-1972, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 24)
  - PLANS 1973-2003, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 25)
  - PLANS 2004-2048, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 11, Folder 30)
  - PLANS 2049-2085, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 11, Folder 28)
  - PLANS 2115-2136, 2217, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 26)
  - PLANS 2137-2159, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 27)
  - PLANS 2160-2187, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 11, Folder 34)
  - PLANS 2188-2216, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 11, Folder 31)
  - PLANS 2218-2302, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 8, Folder 59)
  - PLANS 2303-2352, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 8, Folder 60)
  - PLANS 2353-2380, 2382-2405, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 17)
  - PLANS 2406-2457, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 6, Folder 18)
  - PLANS 2459-2498, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 9, Folder 76)
  - PLANS 2499-2537, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 9, Folder 77)
  - PLANS 2538-2570, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 7, Folder 48)
  - PLANS 2571-2612, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 8, Folder 49)
  - PLANS 2631-2660, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 7, Folder 37)
  - PLANS 2661-2701, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 7, Folder 38)
  - PLANS 2702-2731, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 7, Folder 39)
  - PLANS 2732-2765, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 7, Folder 35)
  - PLANS 2766-2797, 2799, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 9, Folder 74)
  - PLANS 2800, 2802-2820, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer Q 9, Folder 75)
  - PLANS 2806-2114, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer F 12, Folder 40)
  - set of elevations for HVAC system in FF headquarters in NYC, 1968; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 14) (Drawer J 4, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Development Council, Inc., 16
  - 2 copies of "The Essentials for Agricultural Development." Poster describing vital agricultural innovations., POSTER (Quantity 2) (Drawer C 1, Folder 2)
  - 2 copies of "Accelerators of Agricultural Development." Poster describing agricultural development., POSTER (Quantity 2) (Drawer C 1, Folder 2)
  - 2 copies of "Elements of Agriculture." Poster describing agricultural principles., POSTER (Quantity 2) (Drawer C 1, Folder 2)
  - 2 copies of "Agriculture gets its energy from the Sun/ Agricultural development gets it energy from Persons". Poster encouraging agricultural development., POSTER (Quantity 2) (Drawer C 1, Folder 2)
- American Council for the Arts in Education, 17
  - Cleartype Outline Map of the United States., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 1, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund, 19
  - Child Health Demonstrations, 19.1
    - Child Health Demonstration. Lithograph, Austria, 1927; POSTER (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 3, Folder 1)
    - Child Health Demonstration. One small map/painting, two small photographs, Austria, 1924; PRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 3, Folder 3)
    - Child Health Demonstration. Small B & W prints, Austrian, PRINT (Quantity 5) (Drawer B 3, Folder 3)
    - Child Health Demonstration. Map and City Guide of Graz, Austria, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 3)
    - Child Health Demonstration. Map/plan of Frankfurt, Germany., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 3)
    - Child Health Demonstration. Map of Salzburg., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 3)
    - Child Health Demonstration, Pen and ink map of Austria, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 4)
    - Child Health Demonstration - "Commonwealth Fund Map - Activities in Austria", 1936 September 30; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 4)
    - Print and draft version: Commonwealth Fund Child Health Demonstration - "Commonwealth Fund Austrian Child Health Program", 1922; POSTER (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 3, Folder 4)
    - Child Health Demonstration - Austria, Hungary, and Czechoslovakia- Map with Guide (Printed in Great Britain), MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 5)
  - Rural Hospitals, 19.2
    - Rural Hospital Program - Map of Phillips County, Arkansas, 1926 July 10; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Louisville, Georgia Appeal, MAP (Quantity 6) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - South Carolina (Pamphlet) "Kingstreet, South Carolina Appeal", 1937; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - "Mount Carmel, Illinois Appeal". Map of Mt. Carmel, Illinois center, 1946 December 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Laurel, Mississippi, (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of Blackwell, Oklahoma. reverse blueprint, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of Chamberline, South Dakota, 1930 March 19; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of Johnson City, TN. Paper clipped note that reads "Johnson City, Tenn. - Population Map", 1930; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of Sevierville, TN. reverse blueprint, printed: 1934 June; stamped: 1940 April 29; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of Trenton, TN. - Note clipped on to map. Two copies of the map of Gibson County, TN, MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of Union City, TN. Mylar Positives; Commonwealth Hospital Fund, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of San Sava, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
    - Map of Cody, Wyoming. Large folded reverse blueprint of Park County. Small map of "Shoshone Irrigation Project 1924" paper clipped on., 1924. 1932, 1937; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 3, Folder 6)
  - Harkness House Drawings, 19.3
    - original drawings and blueprints from the Harkness House; folder 10 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 1, Folder 10)
      Other Finding Aids note
      For detailed description of Harkness House drawings see:
      FA247 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness House drawings
    - original drawings and blueprints from the Harkness House; folders 1-8, 12, 15, 19-22, 28, 35, 37, 50, 58, 59, 62, 69, 73, 74, 82, 83, 85, 89, 103-105 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 31) (Drawer F 2, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints from the Harkness House; folders 117, 127, 131, 140-142, 167, 168, 176, 177, 178, 181, 187, 203 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 15) (Drawer F 3, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 9, 11, 13, 16, 17, 18, 23, 25, 26, 27, 29, 30 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 12) (Drawer M 1, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 31-34, 36, 38, 39, 41, 43-46, 48, 49 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 14) (Drawer M 2, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 51-57, 60, 61, 63, 64, 66-68, 70-72 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 17) (Drawer M 3, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 75, 76, 78, 79, 81, 84, 86-88, 90-96, 98 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 16) (Drawer M 4, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 99-102, 106-116 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 15) (Drawer M 5, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 118-120, 122-125, 128-130, 133, 134 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 12) (Drawer M 6, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 136, 137, 139, 147-155, 143-145 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 15) (Drawer M 7, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 156-166, 169-172 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 15) (Drawer M 8, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 174, 175, 179, 180, 183-186, 190-196 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 15) (Drawer M 9, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints for the Harkness House; folders 197-200, 202, 204, 206 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 7) (Drawer M 10, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints from the Harkness House; folders 14, 24, 40, 42, 47, 65, 77, 80, 97, 121 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 10) (Drawer Q 2, Folder various)
    - original drawings and blueprints from the Harkness House; folders 126, 132, 135, 138, 146, 173, 182, 188, 189, 201, 205 (Hale & Rogers), 1907; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 11) (Drawer Q 3, Folder various)
- Russell Sage Foundation, 20
  - Forest Hills Gardens: 3 copies of two-sided document: poster, "Birds-eye view of Forest Hills" and architectural lot, "Forest Hills-15 Minutes from Penn Station, Manhattan", 1906 September; POSTER (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Forest Hills Gardens: Map #5 of Forest Hills Gardens. Colored property map of lots sold and lots available., 1918 July; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Forest Hills Gardens: 2 copies of "Map #5 of Forest Hills Gardens." Colored property map of lots sold and lots available., 1913 April; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Forest Hills Gardens: Two-sided document: "Map of location of Forest Hills, " and "Map of Forest Hills", Courd Meyer Developing Company.., 1910; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Forest Hills Gardens: "Forest Hills- 15 Minutes from Manhattan," photographic negative., 1906 September; PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
    Separated from: Series 1059 RSF photographs.
  - Forest Hills Gardens: "Map #5 of Forest Hills Gardens". Uncolored map, copy., 1918 July; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Forest Hills Gardens: "Map #2 of Forest Hills Gardens," colored property map indicating lots sold and contracted. (Sage Foundation Homes Company), 1913 June 19; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Forest Hills Gardens: "Property map of east end of Forest Hills Gardens," property map indicating signed contracts. (Sage Foundation Homes Company), 1913 June 19; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Map #5 of Forest Hills Gardens, 1913 April; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - "Map of Forest Hills Gardens" with duplicate (Russell Sage Home Company), 1911 April; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Forest Hills Gardens: "Blueprint of Jamaica, New York" (Metropolis Engineering Company), 1909 May 30; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Map #5 of Forest Hills Gardens. Colored property map indicating lands sold, reserved, and those not on the market; houses erected., 1915 April 20; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 1)
  - Key Plan of New York and Environs, cartographic map of NYC and surrounding area., 1923 August; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint of Otter Pond, commissioned by Deforest for Mrs. Sage, with duplicate on mylar, 1910 June 4; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 3)
  - Series of 2 blueprints: "Plate 1," subdivision and easement and "Plate 2," location of buildings. (Sunnyside Development of the City Housing Corporation), 1924 August 12; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 3)
  - Map of the City of Yonkers, 1899; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 3)
  - Marsh Island, Parish of Iberia Louisiana, New Orleans, 1904 July 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 3)
  - "Soil Survey of Marsh Island" (US Department of Agriculture), 1911; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 9, Folder 3)
  - Series of 4 blueprints for the "Proposed YMCA Building Along Railroad Bridge Long Island City.", 1932 April 19; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer B 9, Folder 3)
  - "State of Louisiana Geological Survey" (U.S. Dept. of Interior & LA Dept. of Public Works), 1958; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - "Commingling Facilities- Lake Sand Field, Humble Oil & Refining Co. Production Dept." Schematic and duplicate with revisions, 1967 May 25; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    w/ 1968 July 23 Letter, Brian (RDF) to Benson, Box 123, Folder 1171
  - Plat Showing Proposed Well Locations on Various State Leases, with Existing and Proposed Canals. Marsh Island Area, RSF State Game Refuge, Iberia Parish, LA., 1964 February 26; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 122, Folder 1112/ File B-5-R
  - "Pan-American Petroleum Corporation, New Orleans District- Marsh Island Area, Iberia Parish, LA." Property Map., 1964 May 19; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 122, Folder 1160. with J-H-3
  - Preliminary Plat of Cote Blanche, Marsh, Vermillion, & Pecan Islands. Topographical survey indicating well and water locations., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 121, Folder 1156
  - Series of 4 copies of "Plat Showing Proposed Well Locations on Various State Leases, with Existing and Proposed Canals." Marsh Island Area, RSF State Game Refuge, Iberia Parish, LA., 1967 October 11; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 121, Folder 1158
  - Topographic map of Marsh Island, Iberia Parish, LA. Proposed location on wells and canals., 1965 March 30; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - 2 maps showing "Proposed and Temporary Sand Units of the Pan-American Petroleum Corporation." Lake Ferme Fld. Iberia Parish, LA., MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - "Proposed and Existing Units of UL-1B Sand." map made by Humble Oil and Refining Co. Lake Sandfield, Iberia Parish, LA., 1964 August 4; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - Series of 2 maps of Eugene Island, Block 1, indicating property tracts., MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - Series of 2 maps of Eugene Island, indicating property tracts., 1961; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - "Proposed Well Locations", Pan American Petroleum Corporation., 1964 February 26; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 120, Folder 1151
  - "Map of La Salle Parish, Louisiana," colored topographical map. (Army Core of Engineers), 1941; MAP (Quantity 1); adhesive tape residue at the top of the map (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - "Land Leased by the Russell Sage Foundation on Marsh Island" (Louisian Civil Engineer), 1963 April 26; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - 16th Section of Marsh Island, prepared for RSF. Archival Copy., 1957 April 10; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - Partial map of Marsh Island., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Does not include all sections.
  - Partial map of Marsh Island., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - "Proposed Units UL-IB Sand," Marsh Island (Humble Oil and Refining Company), 1962 October 15; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - 2 copies of map of Marsh Island, indicating superior and Humble-owned tracts of land., MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 120, folder 1150
  - "UL-IB RA SU A Lake Sand Field Iberian Parish, Louisiana," map of a land lease on Marsh Island. Archival copy., 1963 April 22; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - Series of 13 maps showing off-shore drill sites of the Humble oil and refining company in Iberia Parish, Louisiana., 1963 April 1; MAP (Quantity 13) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 120, Folder 1149
  - Map of Marsh Island showing competing bids for real estate., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - Map of the Marsh Island Wildlife Refuge, 1963 May 16; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - "Proposed Units UL-IB Sand," map of Humble Oil offshore drilling tracts., 1962 October 15; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
  - Map of Marsh Island separated into two pieces indicating northern and southern tracts., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 9, Folder 4)
    Box 120, folder 1148.
  - "Map #2, Forest Hills Gardens" w/ pencil marks (C.B. Fancy, Civil Engineer), 1912 October; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 14, Folder 3)
  - "Measuring Scale for Handwriting" poster with examples (Department of Education), 1919 September; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
    separated from publications when disbound at RAC
  - "Measuring Scale for Handwriting" poster (Department of Education), GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "Measuring Scale for Adult Handwriting" poster (Department of Education), 1915 February; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - comic strip about drinking clean milk (Department of Child Helping), POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Work of the Remedial Loan Societies for 1912-1913" poster (Division of Remedial Loans), GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Work of the Remedial Loan Societies for 1913 - 1914" poster (Division of Remedial Loans), GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Work of the Remedial Loan Societies for 1914-1915" poster (Division of Remedial Loans), GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Work of the Remedial Loan Societies for 1915-1916" poster (Division of Remedial Loans), GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "Measuring Scale for Ability in Spelling" (Department of Education), 1915 August; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "Measuring Scale for Ability in Spelling" (Department of Education), 1915 April; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "A Scale for Measuring Ability in Silent Reading" P.S 3 and P.S. 4 (Department of Education), 1921 June; GRAPH (Quantity 2) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "A Scale for Measuring Ability in Silent Reading" P.S 1 and P.S. 2 (Department of Education), 1920 April-1921 March; GRAPH (Quantity 2) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "Work of the Remedial Loan Societies" (Department of Remedial Loans), 1914-1915; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "Work of the Remedial Loan Societies" (Department of Remedial Loans), 1915-1916; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
  - "Work of the Remedial Loan Societies" (Department of Remedial Loans), 1916-1917; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer I 2, Folder 1)
    separated from publications when disbound at RAC.
- Archdiocese: Russell Sage Foundation, 21
  - elevation "Details of Screens for Exhibits in Lecture/Exhibition Halls, RSF Building" (scale 1in = 1ft), BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 1)
  - "Riser Sheet, RSF Building" (Neygren Tenney & Ohmes; Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 January 8; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Penthouse Plan, RSF Building" (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Neygren Tenney & Ohmes; Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 January 8; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - set of plans for Lecture Hall & Exhibition Hall (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 April 16; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 8) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Drawing #405: Plan of Lunchroom & Details of Shelves" (scale 1/2 in, 3 in, full size) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 January 5; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Typesheet of (lighting) Fixtures for the RSF" (scale 1/4 full size) (Charles E. Knox), 1913 July 10 and 24; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
    774-F-1
  - "Drawing #425: Detail for Towel Cabinets" (scale 1/4 full size & full size) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1914 March 31; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Drawing #425: Detail for Towel Cabinets" (scale 1/4 full size & full size) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1914 March 31; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Drawing #406: Elevations of Lunchroom #911" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), Revised: 1915 February 10; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Drawing #406: Elevations of Lunchroom #911" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 January 5; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Drawing #254: Library Stack & Reference Rooms Plan" (scale 1/2 in = 1 ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 May 26; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Drawing #219: Library & Reference Room, North & South Elevations" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 April 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - elevation, "Drawing #212: Library & Reference Room, East Elevations" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 April 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - elevation "Drawing #211: Library & Rerefence Room, West Elevations" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 April 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - elevation, "Drawing #414: detail of screens for exhibits in Lecture/Exhibition Halls, RSF Building" (scale 1inch = 1ft) (H.D.V.), 1914 March 10; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - elevation, "Drawing #150: detail of skylight over Exhibition Hall, RSF Building" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 February 11; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - elevation, "Drawing #414: detail of screens for exhibits in Lecture/Exhibition Halls, RSF Building" (scale 1inch = 1ft) (H.D.V.), 1914 March 10, 1914 June 5; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 2)
  - "Drawing #311: Sketch Showing Screen for Stereopticon" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 July 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 3)
  - "Drawing #310; Sketch showing screens for stereopticon, South & East Elevations" (scale 1/2 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 July 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 3)
  - "Drawing #313: Elevation of Exhibition Room" (scale 1/4 in) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 July 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 3)
  - "Drawing #312: Plan of Exhibition Room" (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1913 July 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 3)
  - "Drawing #48: RSF Building: Mezzanine Floorplan (9th) (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 August 26; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #46: RSF Building: 5th (Typical Floorplan)" (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 August 16-1913 April 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #47: RSF Building: Library Floorplan (8th)" (scale: 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 August 16-1913 April 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #46: RSF Building: Typical Floorplan" (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 August 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #46: RSF Building: Typical Floorplan" (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 August 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #46: RSF Building: Typical Floorplan" (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 August 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #46: RSF Building: Typical Floorplan" (scale 1/4 in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 August 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #23: Roof Plan" (scale 1/4in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 July 3 and 10; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #21: Library Floor" (scale 1/4in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 July 3 and 10; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #20: 3rd, 4th, 5th, 6th, 7th, 8th, 9th, 10th Floor Plans" (scale 1/4in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 July 3 and 20; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
  - "Drawing #18: Basement Plan" (scale 1/4in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 July 3; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)
    stamped on reverse: ISSUED 1912 July 15; stamped on reverse "E.G.Soltmann Electric Prints"
  - "Drawing #19: 1st Floor Plan" (scale 1/4in = 1ft) (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1912 July 3; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 4, Folder 4)